[

](https://rslt.io/homepage)

* Solutions
    
    Close Solutions Open Solutions

RSLT LLC

contact@rslt.io

229 East 85th Street, #659

New York, NY 10028

March 15th, 2021

Privacy Policy 

1. General
    =======

This Privacy Policy explains how RSLT collects, uses, and discloses information we obtain through www.rslt.io, and any other websites that we or our business customers use or represent, our advertising attribution platform, and/or any other applications and/or services operated by RSLT that link to this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into RSLT’s Terms of Use. By using our services, you consent to the processing of your information, your client’s information and any consumer information that is collected for our analytics platform as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

2. Background
    ==========

RSLT offers advertisers, agencies, networks and brands a robust analytical platform that enables our business customers to better understand their advertising campaign performance and consumer behavior in connection with TV, radio and online advertising campaigns.

The motivation behind our products is to assist our business customers in better managing their advertising budget so that they would be able to invest in marketing channels that actually work as opposed to those that don’t work well or even underperform. We provide efficiency and budget optimizing platforms that help our clients effectively manage their advertising campaigns based on data we collect and analyse. 

Our data collection methods do not infringe upon the privacy of any client, consumer and/or entity that we collect data upon/from. We do not resell data we collect to any 3rd party companies, we do not track individuals online and we do not make any additional unauthorised and/or undisclosed use of the data we collect. We do not retain the data we collect beyond the period we require to derive insight for our business customers.    

3. Methodology
    ===========

In order to better gauge advertising efficiency and market saturation, we collect a myriad of information from various data sources. We may gather information from our business customer’s websites, publicly available sources, repositories and information provided to us directly by our business customers. 

The information we collect enables us to analyse how effective an advertising campaign is and where advertisers should further invest in order to attain efficient results. We look at big data repositories to understand upper-level consumer behaviours when ads are being aired as well as additional repositories that are publically available.

The collected information is stored on secure RSLT systems that are controlled and monitored using advanced information security mechanisms. These systems are confidential and access to them is strictly limited by function and need.

The information we collect is used to understand consumer response, behaviour, and market saturation. After our analysis is complete, we delete the underlying data but retain the summarized results of our analyses. These summarized results do not contain any Personally Identifiable Information.   

4. Data Retention
    ==============

As part of improving our products and services we retain various databases from time to time. This data retention is primarily for the purpose of helping RSLT adjust and fine tune it’s algorithms, models and code to better serve our customers. 

Additionally, we may retain datasets that contain important information for development of new methodologies for our internal research and development. This data is primarily in the area of saturation of industries across different marketing channels and demographics. The purpose of this retention is to better serve our current and future customers. 

Any data we do retain does not contain any personal identifying information (PII). Personal Identifying Information (PII) is defined as Information that can be used to identify an individual and includes, but is not limited to, the following:

* Full name
    
* Home address
    
* Email address
    
* Social security number
    
* Passport number
    
* Driver’s license number
    
* Credit card numbers
    
* Date of birth
    
* Telephone number
    
* Log in details

The data we retain consists of aggregated metrics of consumers accessing different websites or ‘digital breadcrumbs’ consumers leave when they access the internet. The purpose of this retention is to better understand consumer behaviour and responses to advertising in a variety of scenarios.     

We do not retain any records or establish profiles on specific customers and their browsing patterns online.

5. How we collect information
    ==========================

We may collect and retain any information that customers knowingly provide us when they visit our website. On our website you may provide us with your contact information, including your name, email and phone number, to learn more about our offerings and to schedule demonstrations of our products. 

We automatically collect certain technical information from your computer or mobile device when you visit our website. We may collect information using tags and/or similar technologies. Information collected is stored on secure cloud servers. No identifying information (PII) is stored and access to this information is limited. These tools help us answer our clients needs in regards to advertising performance.

These tools allow us to passively collect information about your computer and/or device, including your web browser type, mobile operating system version (to the extent applicable), and various other properties. We may also collect and store user browser settings and preferences. When our business customers visit our platform, we collect properties indicating which advertising campaign is running, and information about interactions with our platforms.

We automatically collect certain technical information from our business customers’ servers and/or consumers’ computer and/or mobile devices when they use or interact with our business customers’ ads, websites, and/or mobile applications, such as web browser types, browser versions (to the extent applicable), browser settings and preferences, screen sizes, geolocation data, operating system versions, etc.

We may use tags and similar technologies in collecting this information. We also generate our internal IDs, which we create using information about consumers’ computers or devices, including their selected language, screen resolution, plugins, time zones, installed fonts, and similar information. The purpose of this data collection activity is to understand consumer behaviour across different marketing channels without retaining or compromising Personally Identifiable Information (PII).

This information we collect renders consumers, computers and/or additional devices distinct enough for our systems to determine within a reasonable probability how consumers interact with ads in different marketing channels. 

These proprietary data collection tools, which we developed allow us to uniquely identify within high probability, which ads consumers view, hear, click on, and any other interactions with those ads, as well as information about their subsequent visits to our business customers’ websites or their clients. 

We collect this information in order to provide our business customers state-of-the-art insights on the effectiveness of their TV, radio and/or digital advertising campaigns. We may combine the information collected from consumers from different browsers and devices in use in order to provide our services to our business customers.

Our business customers and/or their clients may provide us with additional information they maintain about their customer base, such as demographic or other segmentation information, for use in analyzing the effectiveness of their ad campaigns.

6. Analytics and ad networks
    =========================

We use data from our business customers’ website and application analytics services provided by third parties that collect user data and other similar technologies to collect information about website use and to report trends, without identifying individual consumers. 

We may also collect information from ad network providers (i.e. Adsense, DCM, Facebook, Twitter, etc.) that set and provide access to their platforms in order to collect information about consumer use of a website. 

7. How we use consumer information
    ===============================

We use the information we collect for a number of purposes, including: providing, supporting, and improving our product and services, and for the development of new products and services. We may also use the information we collect to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of consumers without specifically identifying them. 

We use the information we collect when consumers view or interact with our business customers’ ads, websites, and/or mobile applications to measure the effectiveness of our business customers’ ads and share those insights with our business customers. We may combine the information collected from consumers from different browsers and devices in use in order to provide these services to our business customers.

8. How we may disclose information
    ===============================

The information we collect from consumer devices and/or online behaviours, including interactions with our business customers’ ads, websites, and mobile applications, is shared only with the relevant business customer in an aggregated format with no Personally Identifying Information (PII). We do not share this information with anyone else without explicit consent from our business customers. 

For example: We may show our clients that their specific TV ad was viewed by 400K viewers and that 850 consumers from the United States responded to this ad and accessed the clients’ website. We may show how many of these consumers actually converted to paying customers due to the ad/ads aired. We may show from which upper-level geo-locations (city/suburb) did the traffic for the website originate from without disclosing any PII on any consumer. We may show demographic data associated with this traffic as well as additional data metrics that are important to our business customers.

Our business customers may use this information that we provide to further analyze and create a more effective advertising campaign that is better targeted to consumers who are more likely to respond to these ads.

9. Service providers
    =================

We work with third party service providers who provide website development, hosting, maintenance, and support as well as other business services for us. These service providers do not have any access to consumer and/or business customer information we collect or retain.

10. Legal issues
    ============

We do not actively store any information about individual consumers, unless: (i) we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against or respond to physical, financial or other harm, injury, or loss to property; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.

11. Opt out
    =======

If any consumer prefers that we do not collect any information for purposes of providing our advertising analytics services, they may click to opt out on the business customer website. Business customers should keep in mind that their consumers need to separately opt out for each device and/or browser they elect to use. Consumers will need to accept an opt out script in order to exercise their choice; if consumers delete their browser history, they might need to opt out again.

If a consumer does not want us to collect information through the use of tags, their browser may allow them to be notified when they need to execute certain types of tags and restrict or block certain scripts. In addition, if consumers elect to use a new or different browser, they will need to apply the appropriate opt out to that browser. As with the RSLT Opt Out, blocking tags or scripts will opt consumers out of having us collect their information for purposes of providing our advertising analytics services.

12. Safeguards
    ==========

We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the information business customers provide or information we collect against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure, or use. 

13. Children’s privacy
    ==================

We do not knowingly collect any information online from children under the age of 13. If RSLT becomes aware that information collected on any consumer is under the age of 13, we will promptly take steps to delete any information connected to this child. 

14. International and EU
    ====================

Business customers who interact and operate internationally with their consumers (excl. Canada & Mexico) and specifically within the EU, should contact us to receive our Privacy Policy for International and European Union (EU) Business Customers.

15. US and California consumers
    ===========================

If consumers are from the United States, there are additional privacy protections, including: a) the right to see what data we have about consumers, their computer or device (i.e., the right to know), b) the right to delete the data we have about a consumer, their computer or device (i.e., the right to delete) and c) the right to opt-out of the sale of data about a consumer, their computer or device to certain third parties (i.e., the right to opt-out from sales of consumer information). 

We do not discriminate against consumers if they exercise any of the above rights. Moreover, we may not be able to honor a right if doing so would violate applicable law. If consumers want to see what data we may store, such requests need to be sent directly to RSLT at contact@rslt.io.

We do not actively retain any consumer information as listed above, nevertheless consumers are entitled to see and delete any information that we retain or happen to have on them. To do so, please contact us at contact@rslt.io. 

16. Changes to our Privacy Policy and practices
    ===========================================

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to reflect changes in our information practices and/or relevant laws. If we do update this Privacy Policy, we will inform our contracted business customers of any changes and how it may impact ongoing operations.

17. How to contact us
    =================

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices or if you would like to exercise your rights and choices, please contact us through your direct account manager, or at contact@rslt.io or by writing to us at:

RSLT LLC

CONTACT@RSLT.IO

229 East 85th Street, #659

New York, NY 10028

[

](https://rslt.io/)

Pages
-----

Quick Links
-----------

Social Media
------------

[

](https://rslt.io/)

Copyright © 2022. All rights reserved.
